He put the crazy one in,
took the toolbox,
was in the stores and did this.
O good morning.
All good?
I'm from maintenance who's responsible.
Then the crowd all finished.
Damn, it's that veil,
then no, it's João,
then it's the manager,
then João has arrived.
Alright I'm from maintenance I came to do the repair and then I give the team
then I fix bro repair that the guy doesn't know what it is there I put it.
I came here to fix your day.
Let me explain it to you,
man.
My name is Caio and I'm from Brigadier Mano's workshop.
Ha ha ha and that's where I already play here ó,
and this little chocolate ball contains 20g of happiness with this
Pau Face even here so ó how much happiness do you need on your day today?